<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Sales on Imint Investors</title>
    <link>//imintinvestors.com/tags/sales/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Sales on Imint Investors</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2017 22:00:00 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="//imintinvestors.com/tags/sales/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Imint Customers and Products</title>
      <link>//imintinvestors.com/article/20170915-imint-customers-and-products/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2017 22:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//imintinvestors.com/article/20170915-imint-customers-and-products/</guid>
      <description>Background Here&amp;rsquo;s a list of known customers of Imint AB&amp;rsquo;s Vidhance products, along with known products Vidhance is included in. Some of those products have not been communicated by Imint AB themselves. Some have though been communicated by the customer in question, for example on Twitter, and some have been uncovered through firmware analysis.
   Announced Customer Model product Source     2017Q4 Huawei Mate 10* Stabilization Firmware analysis (source)   2017Q3 Vivo X20 Plus Stabilization Press release (source)   2017Q3 Vivo X20 Stabilization Press release (source)   2017Q3 Wiko View Prime Stabilization, Live Auto Zoom Revealed by customer (source1) (source2)   2017Q3 Wiko View XL Stabilization Revealed by customer (source1) (source2)   2017Q3 Wiko View Stabilization Revealed by customer (source1) (source2)   2017Q2 Huawei Honor 9 Stabilization Firmware analysis (source)   2017Q2 Sharp Aquos R Stabilization Press release (source)   2017Q2 BQ Aquaris X Pro Stabilization Press release (source)   2017Q2 BQ Aquaris X Stabilization Press release (source)   2017Q2 Wiko WIM Lite Stabilization, Live Auto Zoom Press release (source)   2017Q2 Wiko WIM Stabilization, Live Auto Zoom Press release (source)   2017Q1 Huawei P10 Plus Stabilization Firmware analysis   2017Q1 Huawei P10 Stabilization Firmware analysis (source)   2017Q1 Huawei Mate 9 Porsche design Stabilization Firmware analysis (source)   2016Q4 Huawei Mate 9 Pro Stabilization Firmware analysis (source)   2016Q4 Huawei Mate 9 Stabilization Press release (source)   2016Q3 BQ Aquaris X5 Plus Stabilization Announced by customer (source)     This phone is still unannounced.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prediction of Huawei&#39;s Vidhance Sales</title>
      <link>//imintinvestors.com/article/20170912-prediction-of-huawei-sales-of-vidhance-models/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2017 15:20:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//imintinvestors.com/article/20170912-prediction-of-huawei-sales-of-vidhance-models/</guid>
      <description>Background Getting detailed information about sales volumes for specific Huawei models is hard. Therefore this analysis is based on the overall picture for smartphone sales from Huawei Consumer Business Group, combined with relevant official communications from Huawei about sales volumes for a few specific models, where such have been obtained.
If unfamiliar with Huawei, this Fortune.com article is a good start.
The bigger picture for Huawei smartphones  2014: 75 million units shipped (source: Huawei) 2015: 108 million units shipped (source: Huawei) 2016: 139.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>