<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Customers on Imint Investors</title>
    <link>//imintinvestors.com/customer/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Customers on Imint Investors</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2017 22:20:00 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="//imintinvestors.com/customer/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Huawei</title>
      <link>//imintinvestors.com/customer/huawei/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2017 22:20:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//imintinvestors.com/customer/huawei/</guid>
      <description>About Huawei Huawei is today the worlds biggest providers of telecommunication equipment. They are also the third biggest smartphone manufacturer selling 139.3 million units in 2016.
History With Mate 9 Huawei was the first device maker to launch a phone with Vidhance Video Stabilization. The launch was preceded by a SEK 800 thousand integration contract followed by an announcement of a license agreement. Huawei was never mentioned by name and that was still the case when Imint proudly proclaimed that there was a phone on the market that used Vidance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vivo</title>
      <link>//imintinvestors.com/customer/vivo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2017 21:22:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//imintinvestors.com/customer/vivo/</guid>
      <description>About Vivo Vivo is a large Chinese technology company that designs, develops, and manufactures smartphones. It was founded in 2009 in Dongguan, Guangdong, China, and as of May 2017, they are the fifth largest smartphone manufacturer in the world according to IDC. Vivo is a sister company of the other smartphone manufacutrors OPPO and IMOO, all wholly owned by the parent company BBK. BBK also (indirectly) owns the company OnePlus, which is a subsidiary of OPPO.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BQ</title>
      <link>//imintinvestors.com/customer/bq/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2017 15:20:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//imintinvestors.com/customer/bq/</guid>
      <description>About BQ BQ is the consumer facing brand of Munda Reader, S.L. a Spanish manufacturer of smartphones with presence in Germany, France, Russia and Portugal. BQ was one of the few device manufacturers that sold phones using Ubuntu Phone instead of Android.
History After BQ had published that their Aquaris X5 Plus phone was going to get Vidhance Video Stabilization Imint confirmed the existence of a license agreement. Although it was the very first license agreement with a device maker Imint announced it took almost a full year until the phone actually got Vidhance Video Stabilization through an firmware update.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sharp</title>
      <link>//imintinvestors.com/customer/sharp/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2017 15:20:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//imintinvestors.com/customer/sharp/</guid>
      <description> About Sharp Sharp is a multinational electronics manufacturer with Japanese origins. They are today owned by the Chinese OEM Foxconn.
History In April 2017 Imint announced a three year license agreement with Sharp. The first announcement did not name Sharp but it was later announced in a second press release.
Devices    Announced Model Product Source     2017Q2 Aquos R Stabilization press release    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wiko</title>
      <link>//imintinvestors.com/customer/wiko/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2017 15:20:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//imintinvestors.com/customer/wiko/</guid>
      <description>About Wiko Wiko is a French smartphone manufacturer. The phones are built in China in corporation with its Chinese majority owner [Tinno Mobile].
History Just before MWC in February 2017 Imint disclosed a multi year license and corporation contract. It was said to also contain product strategic corporations about future Vidhance products. At MWC Wiko announced the Wiko WIM and WIM Lite both featuring Vidhance Video Stabilization as well as Auto Zoom which later that day was confirmed by Imint.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>